(Sheldon:)Oh, look. Saturn 3 is on.
I don't wanna watch Saturn 3.
Deep Space Nine is better.
(Sheldon:)How is Deep Space Nine
better than Saturn 3?
(Raj:)Simple subtraction
will tell you it's six better.
(Leonard:)Compromise. Watch Babylon 5.
[CHUCKLES]
(Sheldon:)In what sense is that a compromise?
(Leonard:)Well, five is partway between three...
Never mind.
(Raj:)I'll tell you what.
How about we go Rock, Paper, Scissors?
(Sheldon:)Ooh, I don't think so.
(Sheldon:)Anecdotal evidence suggests
that in a game of Rock, Paper, Scissors...
(Sheldon:)...players familiar with each other will tie
75 to 80 percent of the time...
(Sheldon:)...due to the limited number of outcomes.
(Sheldon:)I suggest
Rock, Paper, Scissors, Lizard, Spock.
(Girl:)- What?
- It's very simple.
(Sheldon:)Scissors cuts paper, paper covers rock...
(Sheldon:)...rock crushes lizard,
lizard poisons Spock...
(Sheldon:)...Spock smashes scissors,
scissors decapitates lizard...
(Sheldon:)...lizard eats paper,
paper disproves Spock...
(Sheldon:)...Spock vaporizes rock,
and as it always has, rock crushes scissors.